let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one of Santa's reindeer has the same name as another holiday mascot?",
    answer: "Cupid",
    options: [
      "Prancer",
      "Cupid",
      "Comet",
      "Donner"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many ghosts show up in A Christmas Carol?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The movie Miracle on 34th Street is based on a real-life department store?",
    answer: "Macys",
    options: [
      "Macys",
      "Bloomingdales",
      "Saks Fifth Avenue",
      "Westfield"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In Home Alone, where are the McCallisters going on vacation when they leave Kevin behind?",
    answer: "Paris",
    options: [
      "Rome",
      "New York",
      "Paris",
      "London"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What colour Christmas is Elvis going to have?",
    answer: "Blue",
    options: [
      "White",
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Green"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which Hollywood actor played six different roles in The Polar Express?",
    answer: "Tom Hanks",
    options: [
      "Tom Hanks",
      "Richard Attenborough",
      "Tim Allen",
      "Bruce Willis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What are you supposed to do when you find yourself under the mistletoe?",
    answer: "Kiss",
    options: [
      "Dance",
      "Sing",
      "Kiss",
      "Run away"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which real-life person is Santa Claus based on?",
    answer: "St. Nicholas",
    options: [
      "St. Christopher",
      "St. Bernard",
      "St. Jude",
      "St. Nicholas"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In the movie Elf, what was the first rule of The Code of Elves?",
    answer: "Treat everyday like Christmas",
    options: [
      "Treat everyday like Christmas",
      "Check the list twice",
      "There is room for everyone on the nice list",
      "The BEST way to spread Christmas cheer is singing loud for all to hear"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do you say Merry Christmas in Spanish?",
    answer: "Feliz Navidad",
    options: [
      "Nollaig Shona",
      "Feliz Navidad",
      "Marau na Kerisimasi",
      "Meri Kirihimete"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is the best-selling Christmas song ever?",
    answer: "White Christmas by Bing Crosby",
    options: [
      "All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey",
      "Do They Know It's Christmas by Band Aid",
      "Fairytale of New York by The Pogues",
      "White Christmas by Bing Crosby"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What was Frosty the Snowman's nose made out?",
    answer: "A button",
    options: [
      "Corn cob pipe",
      "A button",
      "Coal",
      "A carrot"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What popular Christmas song was actually written for Thanksgiving?",
    answer: "Jingle Bells",
    options: [
      "Jingle Bells",
      "Deck the Halls",
      "Joy to the World",
      "O Holy Night"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What was the first company that used Santa Claus in advertising?",
    answer: "Coca Cola",
    options: [
      "Pepsi",
      "Dr. Pepper",
      "Coca Cola",
      "Mountain Dew"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is The Grinches dog's name?",
    answer: "Max",
    options: [
      "Fido",
      "Charlie",
      "Buddy",
      "Max"
    ]
  },
];
